ILGWU Motion Picture Films 5780 F
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILGWU Motion Picture Films
1952-1987
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union
5780 F
42.89 cubic feet
36 linear ft.
Motion picture (visual works).
This collection consists of films collected, produced or otherwise created by the ILGWU. Included is a DVD copy of a segment of a 1955 broadcast of the Tex and Jinx Show during which ILGWU officials, including David Dubinsky, discuss the work of the union and one of the union's mobile health units is featured.
7461793
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, March 28, 2016
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 02, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union was once one of the largest labor unions in the United States founded in 1900 by local union delegates representing about 2,000 members in cities in the northeastern United States. It was one of the first U.S. Unions to have a membership consisting of mostly females, and it played a key role in the labor history of the 1920s and 1930s. The union is generally referred to as the "ILGWU" or the "ILG". The ILGWU grew in geographical scope, membership size, and political influence to become one of the most powerful forces in American organized labor by mid-century. Representing workers in the women's garment industry, the ILGWU worked to improve working and living conditions of its members through collective bargaining agreements, training programs, health care facilities, cooperative housing, educational opportunities, and other efforts. The ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union in 1995 to form the Union of Needle trades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE). UNITE merged with the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE) in 2004 to create a new union known as UNITE HERE. The two unions that formed UNITE in 1995 represented only 250,000 workers between them, down from the ILGWU's peak membership of 450,000 in 1969.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of films collected, produced or otherwise created by the ILGWU. Included is a DVD copy of a segment of a 1955 broadcast of the Tex and Jinx Show during which ILGWU officials, including David Dubinsky, discuss the work of the union and one of the union's mobile health units is featured.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780: ILGWU records 5780 AV: ILGWU Audio-Visual (AV)
Clothing workers -- Labor unions; Textile workers -- Labor unions
7461793
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Composite B+W Trims" (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Film no.F321 Can 9:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Reel 3 M+E Track, #234" (Box 2)
  Film no.F320 Can 3:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Negative Trims on Healthmobile and Israel" (Box 3)
  Film no.F322 Can 6:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Silent Negative Trims on Citations" (Box 4)
  Film no.F322 Can 3:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Silent Negative Trims on Animation and Inserts" (Box 5)
  Film no.F322 Can 2:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Silent Negative Trims" (Box 6)
  Film no.F322 Can 1:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Work Print of Pix with Opticals Reel 2" (Box 7)
  Film no.F321 Can 8:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Composite B+W Trims" (Box 8)
  Film no.F321 Can 7:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Negative Pix of Stills Trims" (Box 9)
  Film no.F322 Can 5:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Work Print of Pix with Opticals Reel 3" (Box 10)
  Film no.F321 Can 6:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Print of Track Trims" (Box 11)
  Film no.F323 Can 4:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Reel 4 M+E Track, #234" (Box 12)
  Film no.F320 Can 4:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: M+E Print Reel #2" (Box 13)
  Film no.F321 Can 4:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary" (Box 14)
  Film no.F321 Can 3:: M+E Print Reel #3"
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Work Print of Pix with Opticals Reel 1" (Box 15)
  Film no.F321 Can 1:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Prints and Trims" (Box 16)
  Film no.F321 Can 2:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Print of Trims 2" (Box 17)
  Film no.F320 Can 6:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Composite Master Reel 1" (Box 18)
  Film no.F325 Can 2:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: M+E Print Reel #1" (Box 19)
  Film no.F321 Can 5:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Master Trims for Opticals" (Box 20)
  Film no.F323 Can 9:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Composite Master Reel 2" (Box 21)
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: B+W Silent Print of Trims" (Box 22)
  Film no.F324 Can 1:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Composite B+W Print of Trims" (Box 23)
  Film no.F324 Can 2:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Composite B+W Trims" (Box 24)
  Film no.F324 Can 3:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Composite B+W Print of Trims" (Box 25)
  Film no.F324 Can 4:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Composite B+W Print of Trims" (Box 26)
  Film no.F324 Can 5:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Composite B+W Print on J. Wingate Trims" (Box 27)
  Film no.F323 Can 10:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Silent Negative Trims" (Box 28)
  Film no.F322 Can 4:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Composite B+W Print, No Sound Track" (Box 29)
  Film no.F323 Can 11:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Reel 2 M+E Track, #234" (Box 30)
  Film no.F320 Can 2:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: B+W of Pix, Also B+W of Track Trims" (Box 31)
  Film no.F323 Can 5:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Silent B+W Print of Trims on Old Stocks Shots" (Box 32)
  Film no.F323 Can 6:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Composite B+W Print, No Sound Track" (Box 33)
  Film no.F323 Can 7:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Master on Cord to Cord With These Hands" (Box 34)
  Film no.F323 Can 8:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Master Trims on Old Stock" (Box 35)
  Film no.F323 Can 3:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Master Trims of Israel, Old Stock" (Box 36)
  Film no.F323 Can 2:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Print on Pins and Needles Trims" (Box 37)
  Film no.F323 Can 1:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Composite B+W Trims" (Box 38)
  Film no.F323 Can 12:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Print of Trims 1" (Box 40)
  Film no.F320 Can 5:
- Report to Convention, 1986 (Box 41)
  Film no.F66A:
- Report to Convention, 1986 (Box 42)
- "Women of Summer" (Box 43)
  Film no.F226:
- "Fashion Fall & Winter 1960-1961" (Box 44)
  Film no.F230:
- "With These Hands" Print 3 (Box 45)
  Film no.F233:
- "The Many Lengths of Fashion" (Box 46)
  Was box 261. - Film no.F261:
- "Who Makes Your Clothes?" (Box 47)
  Film no.F308:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: B+W Work Print Reel #3 Pix" (Box 48)
  Film no.F329 Can 4:
- Miscellaneous Filmstrips: Case no.2 (Box 49)
- Miscellaneous Filmstrips: Case no.4 (Box 50)
- "With These Hands" Replacements (Box 51)
- "Your Greatest Chance" (Box 56)
  Film no.F305:
- "With These Hands" (Box 57)
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Windgate Trims" (Box 58)
  Film no.F318 Can 5:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Reel 1 M+E Track, #234" (Box 59)
  Film no.F320 Can 1:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Convention Voice Reel 3" (Box 60)
  Film no.F319 Can 6:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Convention Voice Reel 2" (Box 61)
  Film no.F319 Can 7:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Convention Voice Reel 1" (Box 62)
  Film no.F319 Can 5:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Reel 4 Effects Track" (Box 63)
  Film no.F319 Can 1:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Reel 3 Effects Track" (Box 64)
  Film no.F319 Can 2:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Reel 2 Effects Track" (Box 65)
  Film no.F319 Can 4:
- "1959 ILGWU Convention" (Box 66)
  Film no.F317:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Pix and Trims for Opticals" (Box 67)
  Film no.F318 Can 6:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Composite Master Reel 4" (Box 68)
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: With These Hands Trims" (Box 69)
  Film no.F318 Can 4:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: On Title Optics" (Box 70)
  Film no.F318 Can 3:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Pins and Needles Trims, Singing" (Box 71)
  Film no.F318 Can 2:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: 7th Ave Workers" (Box 72)
  Film no.F318 Can 1:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Pix Crowd" (Box 73)
  Film no.F318 Can 7:
- "Incontro Del Lavoro Italo-Americano" (Box 74)
  Film no.F314:
- "Incontro Del Lavoro Italo-Americano" (Box 75)
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Reel 1 Effects Track" (Box 76)
  Film no.F319 Can 3:
- "With These Hands" (Box 81)
- "With These Hands" (Box 82)
- "With These Hands" (Box 83)
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Composite Master Reel 3" (Box 85)
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Composite Master of Trims Reels 1-4" (Box 93)
  Film no.F325 Can 1:
- How Unions & Employers Bargain Together (Box 103)
- "Fashion Means Business" (Box 104)
  Film no.F259:
- "With These Hands" Replacement Footage (Box 115)
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Work Print of Track Reel #3 B+W" (Box 116)
  Film no.F328 Can 5:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Work Print of Track Reel #2 B+W" (Box 118)
  Film no.F328 Can 3:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Composite B+W Print on Trims" (Box 120)
  Film no.F328 Can 2:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Negative Track From Record" (Box 121)
  Film no.F327 Can 6:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Negative Track From Record" (Box 122)
  Film no.F327 Can 5:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Composite Negative, No Sound on Track" (Box 123)
  Film no.F327 Can 3:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Work Print of Track Reel #4 B+W" (Box 124)
  Film no.F328 Can 6:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Silent Negative Trims" (Box 125)
  Film no.F327 Can 2:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Work Print of Track Reel #1 B+W" (Box 126)
  Film no.F328 Can 4:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Composite Negative Pix Trims (Box 127)
  Film no.F326 Can 6:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Composite Negative Trims (Box 128)
  Film no.F326 Can 5:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Composite Negative Pix Trims (Box 129)
  Film no.F326 Can 4:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Composite Negative on Windgate Trims" (Box 130)
  Film no.F326 Can 2:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Composite Negative Pix Trims (Box 131)
  Film no.F326 Can 3:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Silent Negative Trims on Old Stock F7" (Box 132)
  Film no.F326 Can 1:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Sound Statement Composite Negative, No Sound on Track" (Box 133)
  Film no.F327 Can 4:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Composite B+W Print of J. Windgate Trims" (Box 139)
  Film no.F328 Can 1:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: Negative Track of Pins and Needles Singing" (Box 141)
  Film no.F327 Can 1:
- "Miscellaneous" (Box 142)
  Film no.F330:
- "Odds & Ends" (Box 143)
  Film no.F331:
- "Miscellaneous" (Box 144)
  Film no.F332:
- "25th Anniversary of David Dubinsky's Presidency (Box 146)
  Film no.F168:
- "25th Anniversary of David Dubinsky's Presidency (Box 147)
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: B+W Work Print Reel #2 Pix" (Box 148)
  Film no.F329 Can 3:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: B+W Work Print Reel #1 Pix" (Box 149)
  Film no.F329 Can 2:
- "Dubinsky 25th Anniversary: B+W Work Print Reel #4 Pix" (Box 150)
  Film no.F329 Can 1:
- Report to Convention, 1986 (Box 153)
  Was container 66 -- Film no.F66A:
- Miscellaneous Dailies (Box 154)
  Was container 118 -- Film no.F118:
- Pix and Trim Dailies (Box 155)
  Was container 119 -- Film no.F119: Reel 5,
- Pix and Trim Dailies (Box 156)
  Was container 120 -- Film no.F119: Reel 2,
- Pix and Trim Dailies (Box 157)
  Was container 121 -- Film no.F119: Reel 3,
- Pix and Trim Dailies (Box 158)
  Was container 122 -- Film no.F119: Reel 6,
- "ILGWU Convention" A&B (Box 159)
  Was container 123 -- Film no.F123:
- "ILGWU Convention" A&B (Box 160)
  Was container 124 -- Film no.F123:
- "ILGWU Convention" (Box 163)
  Was container 127 -- Film no.F127 and no.F128:
- Pix and Trim Dailies (two films in one can) (Box 165)
  Was container 129 -- Film no.F129 and no.F130: Reel 6,
- "ILGWU" (Box 167)
  Was container 131 -- Film no.F131 and no.F132:
- "Local 32, Vacation Checks" (1952) (Box 169)
  Was container 133 -- Film no.F133:
- "Les Midinettes (1971)" (French) (Box 171)
  Was container 165 -- Film no.F165:
- "Les Midinettes (1971)" (French) (Box 172)
  Was container 166 -- Film no.F165:
- "Around the World" (English) (Box 173)
  Was container 167 -- Film no.F167:
- "25th Anniversary of David Dubinsky's Presidency (1957)" Print 1 & 2 (Box 174)
  Was container 168A -- Film no.F168:
- "25th Anniversary of David Dubinsky's Presidency (1957)" Print 1 & 2 (Box 175)
  Was container 168B -- Film no.F168:
- "50th Anniversary Golden Jubilee Convention" (Box 176)
  Was container 169 -- Film no.F169:
- "Automation" Part 1 (Box 177)
  Was container 170.1 -- Film no.F170:
- "Automation" Part 2 (Box 178)
  Was container 170.2 -- Film no.F170:
- "Automation" Part 3 (Box 179)
  Was container 170.3 -- Film no.F170:
- "Our Electoral Day Illusions: The Beat Majority" Part 1 (Box 180)
  Was container 171 -- Film no.F171:
- "Before the Day" (Box 181)
  Was container 172 -- Film no.F172:
- "Local Issue: Birth of a Union" (Box 182)
  Was container 173 -- Film no.F173:
- "Building Union Participation in Politics" (Box 183)
  Was container 174 -- Film no.F174:
- "The Burden of Truth" (Box 184)
  Was container 175.1 -- Film no.F175:
- "The Burden of Truth" Part I (Box 185)
  Was container 175.2 -- Film no.F175:
- "A Case of Insubordination" (Box 186)
  Was container 176 -- Film no.F176:
- "The Challenge" Print 2 (Box 187)
  Was container 177.2 -- Film no.F177:
- "The Challenge" Print 3 (Box 188)
  Was container 177.3 -- Film no.F177:
- "Contract, Contract" (Box 189)
  Was container 178 -- Film no.F178:
- "1940 ILGWU Convention" (Box 190)
  Was container 179.1 -- Film no.F179:
- "1940 ILGWU Convention" 2 (Box 191)
  Was container 179.2 -- Film no.F179:
- "A Conversation with Dr. J. Robert Oppenheim (Box 192)
  Was container 180 -- Film no.F180:
- "The Count Down" (Box 193)
  Was container 181 -- Film no.F181:
- "Crossroads for America" (Box 194)
  Was container 182 -- Film no.F182:
- Dress Parade" (Box 195)
  Was container 183 -- Film no.F183:
- "The Emerging Woman" (Box 196)
  Was container 184 - Film no.F184:
- "The Extremists" (Box 197)
  Was container 185 - Film no.F185:
- "The Global Assembly Line" (Box 198)
  Was container 186 - Film no.F186:
- "Great Expectations" Part III (Box 199)
  Was container 187.2
- "Great Expectations" Part II (Box 200)
  Was container 187.3
- "The High Wall" (Box 201)
  Was container 188
- "Horizons" (Box 202)
  Was container 189
- "Huelga" Part I (Box 203)
  Was container 190
- "Huelga" Part I (Box 204)
- "Huelga" Part II (Box 205)
  Was container 191
- "Huelga" Part II (Box 206)
- "John F. Kennedy's Last Words to Labor" (Box 207)
  Was container 192
- "Label on Fashion #3" (Box 208)
  Was container 193
- "Last Grave to Dimbaza" 1 (Box 209)
  Was container 194.1
- "Last Grave to Dimbaza" 2 (Box 210)
  Was container 194.2
- "Local 100" Print 2 (Box 211)
  Was container 195
- "Local 100" (Box 212)
- "Maria" Copy A (Box 213)
  Was container 196.1
- "Maria" Copy A (Box 214)
  Was container 196.2
- "Maria" Copy B (Box 215)
  Was container 197
- "Maria" Copy B (Box 216)
- "Maria" Copy B (Box 217)
- "Maria" Copy B (Box 218)
- "Maria" Copy A (Box 219)
- "Jinx's Diary: Mobile Health Unit, Tex and Jinx" (Box 220)
  Was container 198
- "Jinx's Diary: Mobile Health Unit, Tex and Jinx" (Box 221)
  Was container 199
- "The Murrow-McCarthy Debate" (Box 222)
  Was container 200
- "The Organizer" Reel 2 (Box 223)
  Was container 201.1
- "The Organizer" Reel 3 (Box 224)
  Was container 201.2
- "The Organizer" Reel 4 (Box 225)
  Was container 201.3
- "The Organizer" Reel 1 (Box 226)
  Was container 201.4
- "The Other Paris" (Box 227)
  Was container 202
- "Our Union: Local 91" (Box 228)
  Was container 203
- "Our Union: Local 91" (Box 229)
  Was container 204
- "People, Precincts, Power: The Arithmetic of Politics" (Box 230)
  Was container 205
- "The People vs. Willie Farah" (Box 231)
  Was container 206.1
- "The People vs. Willie Farah" (Box 232)
  Was container 206.2
- "Poverty in the Valley of Plenty" (Box 233)
  Was container 207
- "Prosperity for All" (Box 234)
  Was container 208
- "The Rise of Labor" (Box 235)
  Was container 209
- "The Rise of Labor" (Box 236)
- "Roots of Happiness" (Box 237)
  Was container 210
- "Si, Se Puede: Yes, It Can Be Done" (Box 238)
  Was container 212
- "The Stevenson Story" (Box 239)
  Was container 213
- "The Story of 91" (Box 240)
  Was container 214
- "Sunday Show: ILGWU President Sol Chaikin" (Box 241)
  Was container 215
- "Talking Union" (Box 242)
  Was container 216
- "Their Great Adventure" (Box 243)
  Was container 217
- "This is the SIU" (Box 244)
  Was container 218
- "This Union Cause" (Box 245)
  Was container 219
- "This Union Cause" (Box 246)
- "Count: Voter Education Project" (Box 247)
  Was container 220
- "Danny" (Box 248)
  Was container 221
- "What Price Health" (Box 249)
  Was container 222
- "A Watch for Joe" (Box 250)
  Was container 223
- "When the Day's Work is Done" (Box 251)
  Was container 224
- "Wisconsin Story" (Box 252)
  Was container 225
- "Women of Summer" (Box 253)
  Was container 226
- "Youth Wants to Know" (Box 254)
  Was container 227
- "Fashion Pictures 1960" (Box 255)
  Was container 228
- "Fashion Pictures 1960" (Box 256)
- "Fashion: Spring 1960" (Box 257)
- "Fashion Fall & Winter 1960" (Box 258)
  Was container 229
- "Fashion Fall & Winter 1960" (Box 259)
- "Fashion Fall & Winter 1960-1961" (Box 260)
  Was container 230.1
- "Fashion Fall & Winter 1960-1961" (Box 261)
  Was container 230.2
- "Spring & Summer Fashion 1965" (Box 262)
  Was container 231
- "Spring & Summer Fashion 1965" (Box 263)
- "Spring & Summer Fashion 1962" (Box 264)
  Was container 232
- "Fashion Spring Summer 1962" (Box 265)
- "With These Hands" (Greek) (Box 266)
  Was container 233
- "With These Hands" (Box 267)
- "With These Hands" (Spanish) (Box 268)
- "With These Hands" (Italian) (Box 269)
- "With These Hands" (French) (Box 270)
- "With These Hands" (Cantonese) (Box 271)
- "With These Hands" (Box 272)
- "With These Hands" (Box 273)
- "With These Hands" (Box 274)
- "With These Hands" (Germany) (Box 275)
- "With These Hands" (Spanish) (Box 276)
- "With These Hands" (Box 277)
- "With These Hands" (Germany) (Box 278)
- "With These Hands" (Box 279)
- "With These Hands" (Spanish) (Box 280)
- "With These Hands" Replacement footage (Box 281)
- "With These Hands" (Cantonese) (Box 282)
- "First Aid Course" (Box 283)
  Was container 234
- "The Anthem of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union" (Box 284)
  Was container 237
- "Americans All" (Box 285)
  Was container 238
- "The American Issues Forum" (Box 286)
  Was container 239
- "American at Work" (Box 287)
  Was container 240
- "Battle of Wall Street" (Box 288)
  Was container 241
- "Meany Barkan" (Box 289)
  Was container 242
- "Broken Promises" (Box 290)
  Was container 243.1
- "Broken Promises" (Box 291)
  Was container 243.2
- "Brotherhood of Man" (Box 292)
  Was container 244
- "Cast Me Not Off" (Box 293)
  Was container 245
- "The Congress" (Box 294)
  Was container 246
- "Dedication of Penn Station South" (Box 295)
  Was container 247
- "Does it Matter what you think?" (Box 296)
  Was container 248
- "Dues and the Union" (Box 297)
  Was container 249
- "Dutch Team" (Box 298)
  Was container 250
- "Dutch Team" (Box 299)
- "Earthquake in Equador" (Box 300)
  Was container 251
- "European Labor Day" (Box 301)
  Was container 252
- "European Labor Day" (Box 302)
- "Fight for My Union? Damn Right I Would" (Box 303)
  Was container 253
- "The Fine Art of Fraud" (Box 304)
  Was container 254
- "American Fashions: Fall and Winter Fashion 1962-1963" (Box 305)
  Was container 255.1
- "American Fashions: Fall and Winter Fashion 1962-1963" (Box 306)
  Was container 255.2
- "Fashions in the USA" (Box 307)
  Was container 256
- "Fashion USA Spring & Summer 1963" (Box 308)
  Was container 257
- "Fashion in Action" (Box 309)
  Was container 258
- "Fashion in Action" (Box 310)
- "Fashion Means Business" (Box 311)
  Was container 259
- "Fashion Institute of Technology" (Box 312)
  Was container 260
- "The Many Lengths of Fashion" (Box 313)
  Was container 261
- "The Many Lengths of Fashion" (Box 314)
- "Fiddle-De-Dee" (Box 315)
  Was container 262
- "The Fight for Better Schools" (Box 316)
  Was container 263
- "The Fourth Battle of Winchester" (Box 317)
  Was container 264
- "For All The Rest of Your Life" (Box 318)
  Was container 265
- "Highlights of the United Nations" (Box 319)
  Was container 266
- "The Happy Warrior" (Box 320)
  Was container 267
- "Health, Education, and Politics" COPE Film #3 (Box 321)
  Was container 268
- "How to Bury Taft-Hartley" (Box 322)
  Was container 269
- "Local 91" (Box 323)
  Was container 270
- "Los Angeles Health Center Opening" (Box 324)
  Was container 271
- "Magic State" (Box 325)
  Was container 272
- "60 Minutes: Made in Japan" (Box 326)
  Was container 273
- "Marching Towards Tomorrow" (Box 327)
  Was container 274
- "Marvin Has it Made" (Box 328)
  Was container 275
- "Marvin Has it Made" (Box 329)
- "Millions of Us" (Box 330)
  Was container 276
- "Needles and Pins" (Box 331)
  Was container 277
- "Neighbors" (Box 332)
  Was container 278
- "New Americans" (Box 333)
  Was container 279
- "Nine to Five" (Box 334)
  Was container 281
- "Organizing Begins at Home" (Box 335)
  Was container 282
- "The Fox and the Owl" (Box 336)
  Was container 283
- "The Phony Issues, The Real Issues and You" (Box 337)
  Was container 284
- "Politics and the Rigged Tax System" (Box 338)
  Was container 285
- "Camera On Labour: New Health Service for Garment Workers, Steelworkers Go To Press" (Box 339)
  Was container 286
- "The Power Behind the Nation" (Box 340)
  Was container 287
- "The Supreme Court" (Box 341)
  Was container 288
- "The Presidency" (Box 342)
  Was container 289
- "Report on Japan" (Box 343)
  Was container 290
- "Rip-Off At The Top" (Box 344)
  Was container 291
- "Rip-Off At The Top" (Box 345)
- "The Rise of Organized Labor" (Box 346)
  Was container 292
- "The Shoemaker and the Hatter" (Box 347)
  Was container 293
- "Shop Steward" (Box 348)
  Was container 294
- "Support Stronger Social Security" (Box 349)
  Was container 295
- "Support Stronger Social Security" (Box 350)
- "Sam'l and Social Security" (Box 351)
  Was container 296
- "The Sydenham Plan" (Box 352)
  Was container 297
- "Tall Tales" (Box 353)
  Was container 298
- "They Fought for You" (Box 354)
  Was container 299
- "They Fought for You" (Box 355)
- "They Need to Know" (Box 356)
  Was container 300
- "This is the Saar" (Box 357)
  Was container 301
- "Your Greatest Chance" (Box 358)
  Was container 301. Not on shelf, 27Aug14/RDM.
- "Unity House" (Box 359)
  Was container 302
- "Women's Voices: The Gender Gap Movie" (Box 360)
  Was container 303
- "Words from a True Friend of Workers and Their Unions" (Box 361)
  Was container 304
- "Your Greatest Chance" (Box 362)
  Was container 305. Not on shelf, 27Aug14/RDM.
- "Your Next President" (Box 363)
  Was container 306
- "Your Social Security Number" (Box 364)
  Was container 307
- "Who Makes Your Clothes?" (Box 365)
  Was container 308
- "Victims of the Veto" (Box 366)
  Was container 309
- "Victims of the Veto" (Box 367)
- "Victims of the Veto" (Box 368)
  Was container 309. Not on shelf, probably a duplicate entry, 27Aug14/RDM.
- "Victims of the Veto" (Box 369)
- "We Come to Bat" (Box 370)
  Was container 310
- "We Come to Bat" (Box 371)
- "We Come to Bat" (Box 372)
  Was container 310. Not on shelf, probably a duplicate entry, 27Aug14/RDM.
- "We Come to Bat" (Box 373)
- "We the People" (Box 374)
  Was container 311
- "We the People" (Box 375)